Jerry Lewis Papers
National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress
Jerry Lewis papers 1951-2011 1956-2005
Lewis, Jerry, 1926-2017
approximately 45,650 items
220 containers
66 linear feet
Moving Image Research Center, National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
The Jerry Lewis Papers consist of scripts and sketch material; memos and other correspondence; itineraries; business and legal papers; photographic prints, proof sheets, and negatives; press clippings and publicity; and other materials related to the film and television career of comedian, actor, and filmmaker Jerry Lewis, primarily from the period following the breakup of the act he formed with singer and comedian Dean Martin. Also included are papers related to Lewis's work with the Muscular Dystrophy Association's annual telethon, and his teaching work at the University of Southern California.
Provenance
Gift (Jerry Lewis), Jan. 2019.
Accruals
No further accruals are expected.
Transfers
Musical scores have been transferred to the Music Division where they are identified as part of the Jerry Lewis collection.
Other Repositories
Jerry Lewis donated papers related to his film career to the University of Southern California in 1969, where they reside as part of the Cinematic Arts Library.
Material Cataloged Separately
Film and video recordings from the Jerry Lewis Collection have been incorporated into the moving image collections of the Library of Congress Moving Image Section. For additional information, contact a reference librarian in the Moving Image Research Center, National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress, Washington, DC, 20540-4690; (202) 707-8572.
Access and Restrictions
The Jerry Lewis Papers are open to research. Select material may be restricted based on the presence of personal or sensitive information. Advance notice is required; contact a reference librarian in the Moving Image Research Center, National Audio-Visual Conservation Center, Library of Congress, Washington, DC, 20540-4690; (202) 707-8572.
Biographical Note
Comedian, actor, and filmaker Jerry Lewis was born Joseph Levitch in Newark, New Jersey, Mar. 16, 1926. Beginning in 1946, his partner act with Dean Martin, popularly known as Martin and Lewis, were successively among the most popular entertainers in nightclubs, radio, film, and television. Following a professional breakup with Martin, Jerry Lewis embarked on a solo film and television career from 1957-1971. During this period, Lewis increased the scope of his work to include screenwriting, directing, and producing, becoming the total filmmaker, as summed up in his monograph of that title. Sporadic film roles resumed in 1980. Later in his career, Lewis made a critically acclaimed transition to the stage, playing the devil in the Broadway revival of Damn Yankees, beginning in 1995. He died August 20, 2017.
Date Event
1926, Mar. 16 Jerry Lewis born as Joseph Levitch in Newark, New Jersey
1946, July 25 Dean Martin and Jerry Lewis debut as a team at Atlantic City's 500 Club
1948 1953 The Martin and Lewis Show on the National Broadcasting Company radio network
1949 Martin and Lewis are featured supporting actors in My Friend Irma
1950 Martin and Lewis reprise their roles in My Friend Irma Goes West Martin and Lewis are in starring roles for At War with the Army
1951 Martin and Lewis in That's My Boy
1952 Martin and Lewis in Sailor Beware, Jumping Jacks, and The Stooge
1953 Martin and Lewis in Scared Stiff, The Caddy, and Money from Home
1954 Martin and Lewis in Living It Up and 3 Ring Circus
1955 Martin and Lewis in You're Never Too Young and Artists and Models
1956 Martin and Lewis in Pardners and Hollywood or Bust
1954 Martin and Lewis in Living It Up and 3 Ring Circus
1957 Jerry Lewis makes his solo film debut in The Delicate Delinquent and The Sad Sack
1958 Jerry Lewis in Rock-a-Bye Baby and The Geisha Boy
1959 Jerry Lewis in Don't Give Up the Ship
1960 Jerry Lewis in Visit to a Small Planet, The Bellboy, and Cinderfella
1961 Jerry Lewis in The Ladies Man and The Errand Boy
1962 Jerry Lewis in It's Only Money
1963 Jerry Lewis in The Nutty Professor and Who's Minding the Store? The Jerry Lewis Show on the National Broadcasting Company television network
1964 Jerry Lewis in The Patsy and The Disorderly Orderly
1965 Jerry Lewis in The Family Jewels and Boeing Boeing
1966 Jerry Lewis in Three on a Couch and Way...Way Out
1967 Jerry Lewis in The Big Mouth
1967 1969 The Jerry Lewis Show on the American Broadcasting Company television network
1968 Jerry Lewis in Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River
1969 Jerry Lewis in Hook, Line & Sinker
1970 Jerry Lewis in Which Way to the Front?
1972 Jerry Lewis films the unreleased motion picture The Day the Clown Cried
1981 Jerry Lewis in Hardly Working
1983 Jerry Lewis in Marti Scorsese's The King of Comedy
1995 Jerry Lewis makes his Broadway debut in the revival of Damn Yankees
Scope and Content Note
The Jerry Lewis Papers consist of scripts and sketch material; memos and other correspondence; itineraries; business and legal papers; photographic prints, proof sheets, and negatives; press clippings and publicity; and other materials related to the film and television career of comedian, actor, and filmmaker Jerry Lewis, primarily from the period following the breakup of the act he formed with singer and comedian Dean Martin. Also included are papers related to Lewis's work with the Muscular Dystrophy Association's annual telethon, and his teaching work at the University of Southern California.
Arrangement
The Jerry Lewis Papers are organized in 7 series:
Series I. Motion Pictures Scripts and Production Materials, 1958-1982
Series II. Television Scripts and Production Materials, 1960-1970
Series III. Itineraries, 1967-1980
Series IV. Office Files and Correspondence, 1956-1999
Series V. Press Clippings, 1950s-2011
Series VI. Scrapbooks, 1951-1977
Series VII. Visual Materials
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Glucksman, Ernest D., 1902-1979.; Lewis, Jerry, 1926-2017--Archives.; Lewis, Jerry, 1926-2017--Photographs.; Lewis, Jerry, 1926-2017.
Subjects
Actors--United States.; Comedians--United States.; Entertainers--United States.
Titles
Ladies man (Motion picture: 1961)
Form/Genre
Clippings (Information artifacts).; Contracts.; Correspondence.; Financial records.; Jokes.; Memorandums.; Newspapers.; Photographic prints.; Press releases.; Promotional materials.; Scrapbooks.; Screenplays.; Television scripts.
Container List
- Series 1. Motion Pictures Scripts and Production Materials, 1958-1982
  - Rock-a-Bye Baby, 1958 (Box-folder 1/1-2)
  - The Bellboy, 1960 (Box-folder 1/3-4)
  - Cinderfella, 1960 (Box-folder 1/5-8)
  - The Ladies Man, 1961 (Box 2-6)
  - It's Only Money, 1962 (Box-folder 1/9-10)
  - Who's Minding the Store?, 1963 (Box-folder 7/1-3)
  - The Patsy, 1964 (Box-folder 7/4)
  - The Disorderly Orderly, 1964 (Box-folder 7/5-6)
  - The Family Jewels, 1965 (Box-folder 7/7-8)
  - The Family Jewels, 1965 (Box-folder 8/1-3)
  - Boeing Boeing, 1965 (Box-folder 8/4-5)
  - Three on a Couch, 1966 (Box-folder 8/6-11)
  - Way Way Out, 1966 (Box-folder 9/1-3)
  - The Big Mouth, 1967 (Box-folder 9/4-12)
  - The Big Mouth, 1967 (Box-folder 10/1-3)
  - Don't Raise the Bridge, Lower the River, 1968 (Box-folder 10/4-10)
  - Hook, Line & Sinker, 1969 (Box-folder 11/1-6)
  - One More Time, also known as Salt and Pepper II, 1970 (Box-folder 11/7)
  - Which Way to the Front, 1971 (Box 12-17)
  - Which Way to the Front, 1971 (Box-folder 18/1-4)
  - Cracking Up, also known as Smorgasbord, 1983 (Box-folder 18/5-6)
- Series 2. Television Scripts and Production Materials, 1960-1970
  - Specials and Guest Appearances, 1960-1970
    - The Jerry Lewis Show, 1960-05-20 (Box-folder 19/1-2)
    - The Steve Allen Show, no. 11, 1961-12-06 (Box-folder 19/3)
      Rundown.
    - The Wacky World of Jerry Lewis, 1962-05-29 (Box-folder 19/4-9)
    - Ben Casey. A little fun to match the sorrow, 1965-03-08 (Box-folder 19/10)
    - The Tonight Show, week starting, 1968-08-19 (Box-folder 19/11)
    - Correspondence for NET special, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - The Jerry Lewis Show, 1963
    - Individual episode scripts and production papers
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 1, 1963-09-21 (Box-folder 20/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 2, 1963-09-28 (Box-folder 20/3-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 3, 1963-10-05 (Box-folder 20/5-7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 4, 1963-10-12 (Box-folder 21/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 5, 1963-10-19 (Box-folder 21/3-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 6, 1963-10-26 (Box-folder 21/5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 7, 1963-11-02 (Box-folder 21/6-7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 8, 1963-11-09 (Box-folder 22/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 9, 1963-11-16 (Box-folder 22/3-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 10, 1963-11-30 (Box-folder 22/5-9)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 11, 1963-12-07 (Box-folder 23/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 12, 1963-12-14 (Box-folder 23/3-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, no. 13, 1963-12-21 (Box-folder 23/6-7)
    - General production papers
      - Crew and personal staff (Box-folder 24/1)
      - Lyric sheets ("duplicate of song book") (Box-folder 24/2)
      - Television deal press and publicity, 1962-11 (Box-folder 24/3)
      - Pre-show press and publicity (Box-folder 24/4)
      - Publicity (Box-folder 24/5)
      - Correspondence and memos (Box-folder 24/6-7)
      - ABC inter-office telephone directory, 1963-07 (Box-folder 24/8)
      - Cancellation (Box-folder 24/9)
      - Memos (Box-folder 25/1)
      - Master log (Box-folder 25/2)
      - Premiere party (Box-folder 25/3)
      - N.A.B.E.T. (National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians) (Box-folder 25/4)
      - Closed-circuit TV press conference, 1963-09-11 (Box-folder 25/5)
      - ABC-TV promos (Box-folder 25/6)
      - Fan mail (Box-folder 25/7)
      - TV notions (Box-folder 25/8)
      - Photographic proofs, 1963-09-05, 13 photographic prints; black and white; 7.5 x 9.5 inches (Box-folder 25/9)
      - Telegrams, Las Vegas, 1963-11 (Box-folder 25/10)
      - Jerry Lewis Theatre, 4 negatives; color; 8 x 10 inches (Box-folder 25/11)
  - The Jerry Lewis Show, 1967-1969
    - Individual episode scripts and production papers
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 1, 1967-08-11, air no. 1, 1967-09-12 (Box-folder 26/1-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 2, 1967-08-18, air no. 3, 1967-09-26 (Box-folder 26/5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 2, 1967-08-18, air no. 3, 1967-09-26 (Box-folder 27/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 3, 1967-08-31, air no. 2, 1967-09-19 (Box-folder 27/4-7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 4, 1967-09-15, air no. 4, 1967-10-03 (Box-folder 28/1-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 5, 1967-09-21, air no. 5, 1967-10-10 (Box-folder 28/5-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 5, 1967-09-21, air no. 5, 1967-10-10 (Box-folder 29/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 6, 1967-09-29, air no. 6, 1967-10-17 (Box-folder 29/4-7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 7, 1967-10-06, air no. 8, 1967-11-07 (Box-folder 30/1-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 8, 1967-10-13, air no. 7, 1967-10-31 (Box-folder 30/5-7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 9, 1967-10-20, air no. 14, 1968-01-02 (Box-folder 31/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 10, 1967-10-27, air no. 9, 1967-11-14 (Box-folder 31/4-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 11, 1967-11-03, air no. 10, 1967-11-21 (Box-folder 32/1-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 12, 1967-11-10, air no. 12, 1967-12-12 (Box-folder 32/5-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 13, 1967-11-17, air no. 11, 1967-12-05 (Box-folder 33/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 14, 1967-11-24, air no. 15, 1968-01-09 (Box-folder 33/3-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 15, 1967-12-01, air no. 21, 1968-02-27 (Box-folder 34/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 16, 1967-12-08, air no. 13, 1967-12-26 (Box-folder 34/4-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 17, 1967-12-15, air no. 16, 1968-01-23 (Box-folder 35/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 18, 1967-12-22, air no. 17, 1968-01-30 (Box-folder 35/3-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 19, 1968-01-11, air no. 18, 1968-02-06 (Box-folder 36/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 20, 1968-01-19, air no. 19, 1968-02-13 (Box-folder 36/3-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 21, 1968-01-26, air no. 25, 1968-04-09 (Box-folder 37/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 22, 1968-02-02, air no. 20, 1968-02-20 (Box-folder 37/4-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 23, 1968-02-23, air no. 22, 1968-03-12 (Box-folder 38/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 24, 1968-03-01, air no. 23, 1968-03-19 (Box-folder 38/3-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 25, 1968-03-08, air no. 24, 1986-03-26 (Box-folder 39/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 26, 1968-03-15, air no. 26, 1968-04-16 (Box-folder 39/3-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 1, 1968-08-02, air no. 1, 1968-09-17 (Box-folder 40/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 2, 1968-08-09, air no. 2, 1968-09-24 (Box-folder 40/4-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 2, 1968-08-09, air no. 2, 1968-09-24 (Box-folder 41/1)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 3, 1968-08-16, air no. 3, 1968-10-01 (Box-folder 41/2-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 4, 1968-08-30, air no. 10, 1968-11-26 (Box-folder 41/6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 4, 1968-08-30, air no. 10, 1968-11-26 (Box-folder 42/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 5, 1968-09-07, air no. 4, 1968-10-08 (Box-folder 42/3-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 6, 1968-09-13, air no. 6, 1968-10-22 (Box-folder 43/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 7, 1968-09-20, air no. 7, 1968-10-29 (Box-folder 43/4-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 8, 1968-09-27, air no. 5, 1968-10-15 (Box-folder 44/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 9, 1968-10-04, air no. 8, 1968-11-12 (Box-folder 44/4-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 10, 1968-10-11, air no. 9, 1968-11-19 (Box-folder 45/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 11, 1968-10-18, air no. 11, 1968-12-03 (Box-folder 45/4-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 12, 1968-11-08, air no. 12, 1968-12-10 (Box-folder 46/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 13, 1968-11-15, air no. 13, 1968-12-17 (Box-folder 46/4)
      - Pick-ups for shows nos. 12 and 13 (Box-folder 46/5-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 14, 1968-12-06, air no. 14, 1969-01-07 (Box-folder 47/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 15, 1968-12-13, air no. 15, 1969-01-14 (Box-folder 47/4-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 16, 1968-12-20, air no. 16, 1969-01-21 (Box-folder 47/6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 16, 1968-12-20, air no. 16, 1969-01-21 (Box-folder 48/1)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 17, 1969-01-10, air no. 17, 1969-02-04 (Box-folder 48/2-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 18, 1969-01-17, air no. 18, 1969-02-11 (Box-folder 48/5-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 19, 1969-01-24, air no. 19, 1969-02-18 (Box-folder 49/1-2)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 20, 1969-02-07, air no. 20, 1969-02-25 (Box-folder 49/3-5)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 21, 1969-02-14, air no. 21, 1969-03-04 (Box-folder 49/6-7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 22, 1969-02-22, air no. 22, 1969-03-11 (Box-folder 50/1-3)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 23, 1969-02-28, air no. 23, 1969-03-25 (Box-folder 50/4-6)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 24, 1969-03-07, air no. 24, 1969-04-01 (Box-folder 50/7)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 24, 1969-03-07, air no. 24, 1969-04-01 (Box-folder 51/1)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 25, 1969-03-14, air no. 25, 1969-04-08 (Box-folder 51/2-4)
      - The Jerry Lewis Show, tape no. 26, 1969-03-21, air no. 26, 1969-04-15 (Box-folder 51/5-7)
    - General production papers
      - A (Box-folder 52/1)
      - A.F.T.R.A. (AFTRA) (Box-folder 52/2)
      - Appearance agreements (Box-folder 52/3)
      - "The Bug" (Box-folder 52/4)
      - C (Box-folder 52/5)
      - Cast and contracts, 1968 (Box-folder 52/6)
      - Cast lists (Box-folder 52/7)
      - Casting (Box-folder 52/8)
      - Closed-circuit affiliate introduction (Box-folder 52/9)
      - Comic names (Box-folder 52/10)
      - Confidential file (Box-folder 52/11)
      - Contracts and legal (Box-folder 52/12)
      - Copy (Box-folder 52/13)
      - Correspondence (Box-folder 52/14-19)
      - D (Box-folder 52/20)
      - Dirty television (Box-folder 52/21)
      - F (Box-folder 52/22)
      - Bob Finkel (Box-folder 52/23)
      - Flophouse sketch (Box-folder 52/24)
      - G (Box-folder 52/25)
      - H (Box-folder 52/26)
      - "Hello Jerry" (Box-folder 52/27)
      - Instant Theatre sketch (Box-folder 52/28)
      - Jerry Lewis itinerary (Box-folder 52/29)
      - J (Box-folder 52/30)
      - K (Box-folder 52/31)
      - Kraft All Star Game (Box-folder 52/32)
      - L (Box-folder 52/33)
      - Las Vegas gags (Box-folder 52/34)
      - Las Vegas material (Box-folder 52/35-36)
      - Leibman & Haas (Box-folder 52/37)
      - Look Magazine (Box-folder 52/38)
      - Los Angeles Herald-Examiner TV Weekly, 1967, Sept. 17-23 (Box-folder 52/39)
      - M (Box-folder 53/1)
      - Material (Box-folder 53/2-3)
      - MDAA crew and correspondence (Box-folder 53/4)
      - Memos, 1968 (Box-folder 53/5)
      - Memos for show no. 4 (Box-folder 53/6)
      - Memos from Jerry Lewis (Box-folder 53/7)
      - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box-folder 53/8)
      - N (Box-folder 53/9)
      - NBC (Box-folder 53/10)
      - NBC executives (Box-folder 53/11)
      - Nielsen, 30 city (Box-folder 53/12)
      - Notes on shows (Box-folder 53/13)
      - Notions for TV (Box-folder 53/14-15)
      - Office (Box-folder 53/16)
      - Operational schedule (Box-folder 53/17)
      - Orchestra (Box-folder 53/18)
      - P (Box-folder 53/19)
      - Pantomimes (Box-folder 53/20)
      - Press (Box-folder 53/21)
      - Production notes (incoming and outgoing) (Box-folder 53/22)
      - Promos (Box-folder 53/23)
      - Quotes (Box-folder 53/24)
      - Rehearsal schedule (Box-folder 53/25)
      - Re-runs (Box-folder 53/26)
      - Pat Rickey (Box-folder 53/27)
      - Rundowns (Box-folder 53/28)
      - S (Box-folder 54/1)
      - Schedule (Box-folder 54/2)
      - Season, first (Box-folder 54/3)
      - Season, second (Box-folder 54/4)
      - Season blueprint, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 54/5)
      - Dick Shawn (Box-folder 54/6)
      - Show furniture (Box-folder 54/7)
      - Show pictures (Box-folder 54/8)
      - Show titles (Box-folder 54/9)
      - Ed Simmons (Box-folder 54/10)
      - Sketches (Box-folder 54/11)
      - Sketches used in the Colgate Comedy Hour TV shows (Box-folder 54/12)
      - Sound effects (Box-folder 54/13)
      - Staff and crew, 1968 (Box-folder 54/14)
      - Staff addresses and phone numbers (Box-folder 54/15)
      - Staff's children (Box-folder 54/16)
      - T, correspondence (Box-folder 54/17)
      - Talent (actors) (Box-folder 54/18)
      - Robert Taylor, publicity (Box-folder 54/19)
      - Dave Tebet (Box-folder 54/20-21)
      - Telegrams and correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 54/22)
      - Tickets, correspondence regarding (Box-folder 54/23)
      - Thank you notes to performers (Box-folder 54/24)
      - V (Box-folder 54/25)
      - W (Box-folder 54/26)
      - Jack Webb (Box-folder 54/27)
      - Mort Werner (Box-folder 54/28)
      - Rusty Wiles (Box-folder 54/29)
      - William Morris Agency (Box-folder 54/30-31)
      - Wires (Box-folder 54/32)
      - The Young Americans (Box-folder 54/33)
      - X--Y--Z, correspondence (Box-folder 54/34)
    - Guild and artist contracts
      - American Federation of Musicians (Box-folder 55/1)
      - AFTRA pension and welfare retroactive payments (Box-folder 55/2)
      - Directors Guil of America (Box-folder 55/3)
      - Talent expense summary forms (Box-folder 55/4)
      - Writers Guild Broadcast Industry health benefit fund (Box-folder 55/5)
      - Writers Guild-Broadcast Industry pension trust fund (Box-folder 55/6)
      - Hal Goodman (and Larry Klein), writers (Box-folder 55/7)
      - Norman Liebman and Ed Haas, writers (Box-folder 55/8)
      - Marty Ragway, writer (Box-folder 55/9)
      - Ed Simmons (Canterbury Productions) (Box-folder 55/10)
      - George Wylie, choral director (Box-folder 55/11)
      - AFTRA reports for season one, episode nos. 1-10 (Box-folder 55/12-21)
      - AFTRA reports for season one, episode nos. 11-26 (Box-folder 56/1-16)
      - Guest entertainers
        Access to materials in box 57 may be restricted or redacted due to personal information. Contact a reference librarian in the Moving Image Research Center for further information.
        - Don Adams (Box-folder 57/1)
        - Nancy Ames (Box-folder 57/2)
        - The Baja Marimba Band (Box-folder 57/3)
        - Kaye Ballard (Box-folder 57/4)
        - Count Basie (Box-folder 57/5)
        - Anne Baxter (Box-folder 57/6)
        - Polly Bergen (Box-folder 57/7)
        - Ernest Borgnine (Box-folder 57/8)
        - The Buckinghams (Box-folder 57/9)
        - Imogene Coca (Box-folder 57/10)
        - Bobby Darin (Box-folder 57/11)
        - The Doodletown Pipers (Box-folder 57/12)
        - Barbara Eden (Box-folder 57/13)
        - Nanette Fabray (Box-folder 57/14)
        - Joey Faye (Box-folder 57/15)
        - Barbara Feldon (Box-folder 57/16)
        - Eddie Fisher (Box-folder 57/17)
        - Paul Ford (Box-folder 57/18)
        - Sergio Franchi (Box-folder 57/19)
        - Zsa Zsa Gabor (Box-folder 57/20)
        - Ben Gazarra (Box-folder 57/21)
        - Arthur Godfrey (Box-folder 57/22)
        - Frank Gorshin (Box-folder 57/23)
        - Robert Goulet (Box-folder 57/24)
        - Merv Griffin (Box-folder 57/25)
        - Noel Harrison (Box-folder 57/26)
        - Laurence Harvey (Box-folder 57/27)
        - Herman's Hermits (Box-folder 57/28)
        - Joey Heatherton (Box-folder 57/29)
        - The Honeys Limited (Box-folder 57/30)
        - Al Hirt (Box-folder 57/31)
        - Jack Jones (Box-folder 57/32)
        - Shirley Jones (Box-folder 57/33)
        - Richard Kiley (Box-folder 57/34)
        - Peter Lawford (Box-folder 57/35)
        - Michelle Lee (Box-folder 57/36)
        - Janet Leigh (Box-folder 57/37)
        - The Lennon Sisters (Box-folder 57/38)
        - Roddy McDowall (Box-folder 57/39)
        - The McGuire Sisters (Box-folder 57/40)
        - Audrey Meadows (Box-folder 57/41)
        - Sergio Mendes and Brasil '66 (Box-folder 57/42)
        - Anna Moffo (Box-folder 57/43)
        - Ricardo Montalban (Box-folder 57/44)
        - Del Moore (Box-folder 57/45)
        - Harry Morgan (Box-folder 57/46)
        - The Osmond Brothers (Box-folder 57/47)
        - Jane Powell (Box-folder 57/48)
        - Dorothy Provine (Box-folder 57/49)
        - Tony Randall (Box-folder 57/50)
        - Martha Raye (Box-folder 57/51)
        - Lynn Redgrave (Box-folder 57/52)
        - Cliev Revill (Box-folder 57/53)
        - Don Rickles (Box-folder 57/54)
        - Thelma Ritter (Box-folder 57/55)
        - Harold Sakata (Box-folder 57/56)
        - Dick Shawn (Box-folder 57/57)
        - Sonny and Cher (Box-folder 57/58)
        - Connie Stevens (Box-folder 57/59)
        - Inger Stevens (Box-folder 57/60)
        - Harold J. Stone (Box-folder 57/61)
        - Mel Torme (Box-folder 57/62)
        - Lana Turner (Box-folder 57/63)
        - Gwen Verdon (Box-folder 57/64)
        - Jack Webb (Box-folder 57/65)